<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Gun Shop</string>
    <string name="logo_alt">Gun Shop logo description</string>
    <string name="guns_logo_description">Guns list</string>

    <!--Main menu guns list-->
    <string-array name="main_gun_list">
        <item>Guns</item>
        <item>Assault rifles</item>
        <item>Sniper rifles</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Guns names-->
    <string name="gun_name_tt">TT pistol</string>
    <string name="gun_name_stechkin">Stechkin automatic pistol</string>
    <string name="gun_name_makarov">Makarov pistol</string>

    <!--Guns descriptions-->
    <string name="gun_description_tt">The TT-30[a] is a Russian semi-automatic pistol. It was developed in the early 1930s by Fedor Tokarev as a service pistol for the Soviet military to replace the Nagant M1895 revolver that had been in use since Tsarist times, though it ended up being used in conjunction with rather than replacing the M1895. It served until 1952, when it was replaced by the Makarov pistol.</string>
    <string name="gun_description_stechkin">The Stechkin automatic pistol or APS (Avtomaticheskiy Pistolet Stechkina = Автоматический Пистолет Стечкина) is a Soviet selective fire machine pistol chambered in 9×18mm Makarov and 9x19mm Parabellum introduced into service in 1951 for use with artillery and mortar crews, tank crews and aircraft personnel, where a cumbersome assault rifle was deemed unnecessary. Seeing service in a number of wars such as the Vietnam war, War in Donbass, and Syrian Civil War. The APS was praised for its innovative concept and good controllability for its size. However, the high cost of the weapon, complex and time-consuming machining, combined with a limited effective range, large size and weight for a pistol, and fragile buttstock have been mentioned as a reason to phase it out of active service in favour of an Assault rifle such as the AKS-74U. The pistol bears the name of its developer, Igor Stechkin.</string>
    <string name="gun_description_makarov">The Makarov pistol or PM (Russian: Пистолет Макарова, Pistolet Makarova, literally Makarov\'s Pistol) is a Russian semi-automatic pistol. Under the project leadership of Nikolay Fyodorovich Makarov, it became the Soviet Union\'s standard military and police side arm in 1951.</string>
    <string name="iv_description">image</string>

    <!--Assault rifles names-->
    <string name="assault_rifle_name_ak74">AK-74</string>
    <string name="assault_rifle_name_m4">M4 carbine</string>
    <string name="assault_rifle_name_aug">Steyr AUG</string>

    <!--Assault rifles descriptions-->
    <string name="assault_rifle_description_ak74">The AK-74 (Russian: Автомат Калашникова образца 1974 года or \"Kalashnikov automatic rifle model 1974\") is an assault rifle developed in the early 1970s by Russian designer Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the earlier AKM (itself a refined version of the AK-47). It uses a smaller 5.45×39mm cartridge, replacing the 7.62×39mm chambering of earlier Kalashnikov-pattern weapons. The rifle first saw service with Soviet forces in the 1979 Afghanistan conflict. The head of the Afghan bureau of the Pakistani Inter-Services Intelligence claimed that the CIA paid $5,000 for the first AK-74 captured by the Mujahideen during the Soviet–Afghan War. Today, the rifle is used by most countries of the former Soviet Union. Licensed copies were produced in Bulgaria (AK-74, AKS-74 and AKS-74U), and the former East Germany (MPi-AK-74N, MPi-AKS-74N, MPi-AKS-74NK).</string>
    <string name="assault_rifle_description_m4">The M4 carbine is a shorter and lighter variant of the M16A2 assault rifle. The M4 is a 5.56×45mm NATO, air-cooled, direct impingement gas-operated, magazine-fed carbine. It has a 14.5 in (370 mm) barrel and a telescoping stock. The M4 carbine is extensively used by the United States Armed Forces and is largely replacing the M16 rifle in United States Army and United States Marine Corps combat units as the primary infantry weapon and service rifle. The M4 is also capable of mounting the M203 and M320 grenade launchers. The distinctive step in its barrel is for mounting the M203 with the standard hardware. The M4 has semi-automatic and three-round burst firing modes (like the M16A2 and M16A4), while the M4A1 has semi-automatic and fully automatic firing modes (like the M16A1 and M16A3).</string>
    <string name="assault_rifle_description_aug">The Steyr AUG (Armee-Universal-Gewehr—\"universal army rifle\") is an Austrian 5.56×45mm NATO bullpup assault rifle, designed in the 1960s by Steyr-Daimler-Puch and now manufactured by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH &amp; Co KG.It was adopted by the Austrian Army as the StG 77 (Sturmgewehr 77) in 1978, where it replaced the 7.62×51mm NATO StG 58 automatic rifle (a licence-built FN FAL). In production since 1978, it is the standard small arm of the Austrian Bundesheer and various national police units. Its variants have also been adopted by the armed forces of dozens of countries.</string>

    <string name="assault_rifles_alt">Assault rifles logo image</string>
    <string name="iv_assault_rifles_image">image</string>

    <!--Sniper rifles names-->
    <string name="rifle_name_dragunov">Dragunov sniper rifle</string>
    <string name="rifle_name_awm">Accuracy International AWM</string>
    <string name="rifle_name_m95">Barrett M95</string>

    <!--Sniper rifles descriptions-->
    <string name="rifle_description_dragunov">The Dragunov sniper rifle (formal Russian: Сна́йперская Винто́вка систе́мы Драгуно́ва образца́ 1963 года, Snáyperskaya Vintóvka sistém\'y Dragunóva obraz\'tsá 1963 goda (SVD-63), officially "Sniper Rifle, System of Dragunov, Model of the Year 1963") is a semi-automatic sniper/designated marksman rifle chambered in 7.62×54mmR and developed in the Soviet Union. The Dragunov was designed as a squad support weapon since, according to Soviet and Soviet-derived military doctrines, the long-range engagement ability was lost to ordinary troops when submachine guns and assault rifles (which are optimized for close-range and medium-range, rapid-fire combat) were adopted.It was selected as the winner of a contest that included three competing designs: by Sergei Simonov, Aleksandr Konstantinov and Yevgeny Dragunov. Extensive field testing of the rifles conducted in a wide range of environmental conditions resulted in Dragunov’s proposal being accepted into service in 1963. An initial pre-production batch consisting of 200 rifles was assembled for evaluation purposes, and from 1964 serial production was carried out by Izhmash, later called Kalashnikov Concern.Since then, the Dragunov has become the standard squad support weapon of several countries, including those of the former Warsaw Pact. China, while having produced an unlicensed copy of the SVD through reverse-engineered samples captured from Sino-Vietnamese War as the Type 79 and 85,[11] never officially purchased or was given SVD Dragunov by the Soviets, as the Sino-Soviet split had already occurred when the SVD entered service and relations were strained between the two, halting further military cooperations and aid. Iran also produced a clone as the Nakhjir 3 (as a direct copy of the Chinese Type 79).</string>
    <string name="rifle_description_awm">The Accuracy International AWM (Arctic Warfare Magnum or AI-Arctic Warfare Magnum) is a bolt-action sniper rifle manufactured by Accuracy International designed for magnum rifle cartridges. The Accuracy International AWM is also unofficially known as the AWSM (Arctic Warfare Super Magnum), which typically denotes AWM rifles chambered in .338 Lapua Magnum.On 9 September 2012, Accuracy International announced that the .338 Lapua Magnum AWM rifle was phased out and replaced by the Accuracy International AXMC sniper rifle.</string>
    <string name="rifle_description_m95">The Barrett M95 is a bolt-action sniper rifle chambered in .50 BMG (12.7×99mm), and manufactured by Barrett Firearms Company. It has been adopted by a number of militaries around the world. The M95 is an improved version of the earlier Barrett M90. It is a bolt-action sniper rifle in a bullpup design. The major difference between the M95 and the M90 is that the pistol grip and trigger have been moved forward 1 inch (25 mm) for better magazine clearance. Also, the bolt handle has been redesigned and bent down and to the rear, the barrel chamber has been plated in chrome, and there are also some minor changes to the trigger and firing pin.</string>
    <string name="iv_rifles_details">image</string>


</resources>
